
{"front":"Which city is the capital of France?","back":"Paris"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of Great Britain?","back":"London"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of Finland?","back":"Helsinki"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of Denmark?","back":"Copenhagen"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of Germany?","back":"Berlin"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of Egypt?","back":"Cairo"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of Italy?","back":"Rome"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of Belgium?","back":"Brussels"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of the Netherlands?","back":"Amsterdam"}
{"front":"Which city is the capital of Norway?","back":"Oslo"}
